<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
    Copyright 2010 Archie L. Cobbs

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may
    not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain
    a copy of the License at

        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT
    WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the
    License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations
    under the License.
-->

<ivy-module rev="$Id$">

    <info publication="20110514120000">
        <license name="GNU Affero General Public License, Version 3.0" url="http://www.gnu.org/licenses/agpl-3.0.html"/>
        <description homepage="http://vaadin.com/directory#addon/lazy-query-container">

            <p>
            Lazy Query Container is a <a href="http://www.vaadin.com/">Vaadin framework</a>
            addon which provides lazy loading container for Vaadin tables. Lazy Query
            Container supports buffered reads and writes of items. Data
            reads and writes are delegated through Query interface to
            an application specific business delegate.
            </p>

            <p>
            The QueryFactory and Query interface implementations are
            designed to be application specific and should invoke a data
            source like WebService client, JDBC connection, JPA context
            or Java service class to read and write data items. The data
            source has to support querying data in batches.
            </p>

            <p>
            Lazy Query Container supports the following features: lazy
            loading of items, loading items in batches, item caching with
            limited cache size, sorting, query statistics, changing item
            set and changing property set. Since version 1.1.0 Lazy Query
            Container also supports adding items, modifying items and
            removing items. The changes are buffered and can be either
            commited or discarded. Row status icons and status column
            generator are also included to allow for visualization of row
            states. See the demo for hands on experience on the features.
            </p>

            <p>
            Specialized classes (see
            <a href="http://vaadin.com/wiki/-/wiki/Main/Lazy%20Query%20Container/">Wiki</a>
            page for examples):
            <ul>
            <li>CompositeItem for combining beans and dynamic properties</li>
            <li>EntityContainer specialized container for easy use of JPA with LQC</li>
                <ul>
                <li>Both container and application managed transactions are supported</li>
                <li>Both attached and detached entities are supported</li>
                </ul>
            </ul>
            <li>BeanQueryFactory for queries loading JavaBeans</li>
            </p>

        </description>
    </info>

    <publications>
        <artifact/>
    </publications>

    <dependencies>
        <dependency org="com.vaadin" name="vaadin" rev="[6.6,7.0[" conf="default->default"/>
    </dependencies>

</ivy-module>
