<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../../xsl/ivy-doc.xsl"?>

<!--
    Copyright 2008 Archie L. Cobbs.

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may
    not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain
    a copy of the License at

        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT
    WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the
    License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations
    under the License.
-->
<!-- GENERATED FILE - DO NOT EDIT -->
<ivy-module xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="2.0" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../xsd/ivy.xsd">

    <info organisation="net.sourceforge.gwt-widget" module="gwt-sl" revision="0.1.4c" status="release" publication="20071207053900">
        <license name="Apache License, Version 2.0" url="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0"/>
        <ivyauthor name="$Id: ivy.xml 544 2009-03-12 11:37:20Z spatialguru.net $" url="http://code.google.com/p/ivyroundup/source/browse/trunk/src/modules/net.sourceforge.gwt-widget/gwt-sl/0.1.4c/"/>
        <repository pattern="http://ivyroundup.googlecode.com/svn/trunk/repo/modules/[organisation]/[module]/[revision]/ivy.xml" ivys="true" url="http://ivyroundup.googlecode.com/" name="ivyroundup"/>
        <description homepage="http://gwt-widget.sourceforge.net/">
            <p>
            The GWT Server Library is a collection of Java server side
            components for the Google Web Toolkit AJAX framework with
            the current focus on the Spring framework by facilitating
            publishing of Spring beans as RPC services. The main binary
            dependencies are GWT 1.4, Spring 2.0 and Commons Logging 1.1.
            </p>

            <p>
            The Spring Framework is an established component framework for
            web applications that span authentication, database access
            and complex page flow. Through its aspect oriented approach
            it is unobtrusive and cleanly separates the presentation
            layer from the business logic and the data model, allowing
            for back end services which have nothing to do with the way
            the presentation is rendered. This is the ideal base for a
            GWT application, which also separates the presentation (your
            widgets that run in the browser) from the business logic
            (your RPC services running on the web server) from the data
            model (the objects serialised over RPC).
            </p>

            <p>
            GWT binds java methods to RPC calls by using the Servlet API
            so that each service you write is a servlet. The Servlet
            API however is rather crude and the servlet container
            (like Tomcat) is a gross environment providing little
            assistance to elaborate tasks like transaction management,
            AOP tasks (authentication, logging, per-task caching)
            etc. Also the notoriously scarce configuration abilities
            are by far inferior to Spring's XML configuration and bean
            injection which allows even the most complex configurations
            by plugging objects together in XML. With the GWT-SL you can
            easily write Spring managed beans which act as GWT services,
            taking full advantage of both frameworks.
            </p>
        </description>
    </info>

    <configurations>
        <conf name="default" description="Default configuration"/>
        <conf name="jdk14" description="Alternate JDK 1.4 configuration"/>
    </configurations>

    <publications>
        <artifact/>
        <artifact name="gwt-sl-java1.4"/>
        <artifact name="source" type="source" ext="zip"/>
        <artifact name="javadoc" type="javadoc" ext="zip"/>
    </publications>

</ivy-module>
