<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
    Copyright 2013 Mark Thomas

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may
    not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain
    a copy of the License at

        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT
    WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the
    License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations
    under the License.
-->

<ivy-module>

    <info publication="20130102133200">
        <license name="Apache License, Version 2.0" url="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0"/>
        <description homepage="http://jamonapi.sourceforge.net/">
            <p>
                The Java Application Monitor (JAMon) is a free, simple, high performance, thread safe, Java API that allows developers to easily monitor production applications.
                <ul>
                    <li>JAMon can be used to determine application performance bottlenecks, user/application interactions, track application scalability, and more.</li>
                    <li>JAMon 1.0 gathers aggregate performance statistics such as hits, execution times (total, average, minimum, maximum, standard deviation), as well as concurrency information such as simultaneous application requests.</li>
                    <li>JAMon 2.7 comes with several ways to monitor your application that require no application code changes. Usually all that is required is to add a line to an xml file, and make the jamon jar file available. Some examples:
                        <ul>
                            <li>JDBC/SQL monitoring via the JAMon JDBC proxy driver (works with any other JDBC driver),</li>
                            <li>Log4j monitoring via the JAMon log4j Appender,</li>
                            <li>HTTP Monitoring. Monitor requests/responses to Tomcat, Jetty, JBoss or any other JAVA web container.</li>
                            <li>EJB3 monitoring using the JAMon EJB interceptor.</li>
                        </ul>
                    </li>
                    <li>JAMon 2.0 aggregates ANY numeric entity (such as bytes sent, dollars purchased, phone call duration) associated with a key (label and units).</li>
                    <li>JAMon 2.1 adds the ability to track both summary statistics and detils for Interfaces/JDBC/SQL/Exceptions.</li>
                    <li>JAMon 2.2 adds the ability to track JDBC/SQL/Exceptions vi the new JAMonDriver JDBC Driver using a URL (not changing code)</li>
                    <li>JAMon 2.3 minor bug fixes</li>
                    <li>JAMon 2.4/2.5 Introduction of JAMon Buffer Listeners to track details of interest such as extreme values, or most recent values</li>
                    <li>JAMon 2.6 log4j monitoring. Track stats on log4j method calls, as well as have the ability to 'tail' data written to log4j through the JAMon web application.</li>
                    <li>JAMon 2.7 Add the ability to flexibly monitor Tomcat, Jetty, Jboss. More flexible detail tracking was added. Also better exception tracking was added.</li>
                    <li>JAMon data can also be programmatically accessed or queried and your program can take actions on the results.</li>
                    <li>JAMon statistics are displayed in the clickable JAMon Report</li>
                </ul>
            </p>

        </description>
    </info>

    <configurations>
        <conf name="core" description="Core classes"/>
        <conf name="tomcat" description="Tomcat classes"/>
        <conf name="default" extends="core" description="Alias for core"/>
    </configurations>

    <publications>
        <artifact conf="core"/>
        <artifact name="jamontomcat" conf="tomcat"/>
        <artifact type="source" ext="zip"/>
        <artifact type="javadoc" ext="zip"/>
    </publications>

</ivy-module>
