<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../../xsl/ivy-doc.xsl"?>

<!--
    Copyright 2009 Mark Thomas

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may
    not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain
    a copy of the License at

        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT
    WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the
    License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations
    under the License.
-->
<!-- GENERATED FILE - DO NOT EDIT -->
<!-- Generated by $Id: ivy-repo.xsl 478 2009-02-20 20:36:35Z archie.cobbs $ -->
<ivy-module xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="2.0" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../xsd/ivy.xsd">

    <info organisation="javax.jnlp" module="jnlp" revision="1.5" status="release" publication="20090117013500">
        <license name="Sun Microsystems, Inc. Binary Code License Agreement" url="http://java.sun.com/products/jms/docs.html"/>
        <ivyauthor name="$Id: ivy.xml 621 2009-03-24 13:44:56Z spatialguru.net $" url="http://code.google.com/p/ivyroundup/source/browse/trunk/src/modules/javax.jnlp/jnlp/1.5/"/>
        <repository pattern="http://ivyroundup.googlecode.com/svn/trunk/repo/modules/[organisation]/[module]/[revision]/ivy.xml" ivys="true" url="http://ivyroundup.googlecode.com/" name="ivyroundup"/>
        <description homepage="http://java.sun.com/javase/technologies/desktop/javawebstart/index.jsp">
        <p>
        Java Web Start is a helper application that gets associated with a Web
        browser. When a user clicks on a link that points to a special launch
        file (JNLP file), it causes the browser to launch Java Web Start,
        which then automatically downloads, caches, and runs the given Java
        Technology-based application. The entire process is typically
        completed without requiring any user interaction, except for the
        initial single click.
        </p>
        <p>
        From a technology standpoint, Java Web Start has a number of key
        benefits that make it an attractive platform to use for deploying
        applications:
        <ul>
            <li>Java Web Start is built exclusively to launch applications
                written to the Java(TM) Platform Standard Edition. Thus, a
                single application can be made available on a Web server and
                then deployed on a wide variety of platforms, including
                Windows 98/NT/2000/ME/XP, Linux, and the Solaris<sup>TM</sup>
                Operating Environment. The Java platform has proven to be a
                very robust, productive, and expressive development platform,
                leading to a significant cost savings due to minimized
                development and testing costs.</li>
            <li>Java Web Start supports multiple revisions of the Java(TM)
                Platform Standard Edition. Thus, an application can request a
                particular version of the platform it requires, such as Java
                SE<sup>TM</sup> 1.5.0. Several applications can run at the same
                time on different platform revisions without causing conflicts,
                and Java Web Start can automatically download and install a
                revision of the platform if an application requests a version
                that is not installed on the client system.</li>
            <li>Java Web Start allows applications to be launched independently
                of a Web browser. This can be used for off-line operation of an
                application, where launching through the browser is often
                inconvenient or impossible. The application can also be
                launched through desktop shortcuts, making launching the
                Web-deployed application similar to launching a native
                application.</li>
            <li>Java Web Start takes advantage of the inherent security of the
                Java Platform. Applications are by default run in a protective
                environment (sandbox) with restricted access to local disk and
                network resources. It allows the user to safely run
                applications from sources that are not trusted.</li>
            <li>Applications launched with Java Web Start are cached locally.
                Thus, an already-downloaded application is launched on par with
                a traditionally installed application.</li>
        </ul>
        </p>
        <p>
        The technology underlying Java Web Start is the Java <sup>TM</sup>
        Network Launching Protocol &amp; API (JNLP). This technology was
        developed via the Java Community Process (JCP). Java Web Start is the
        reference implementation (RI) for the JNLP specification. The JNLP
        technology defines, among other things, a standard file format that
        describes how to launch an application called a JNLP file.
        </p>
        </description>
    </info>

    <publications>
        <artifact name="jardiff"/>
        <artifact name="jnlp"/>
        <artifact name="jnlp-servlet"/>
    </publications>

</ivy-module>
