<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../../xsl/ivy-doc.xsl"?>
<!--
    Copyright 2009 Kirby Files

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may
    not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain
    a copy of the License at

        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT
    WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the
    License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations
    under the License.
-->
<!-- GENERATED FILE - DO NOT EDIT -->
<ivy-module xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="2.0" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../../../xsd/ivy.xsd">

    <info organisation="com.google" module="gwt" revision="2.2.0" status="release" publication="20110210120000">
        <license name="Apache License, Version 2.0" url="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0"/>
        <ivyauthor xmlns:ivyde="http://ant.apache.org/ivy/ivyde/ns/" name="$Id: ivy.xml 1519 2011-03-22 21:09:39Z archie.cobbs $" url="http://code.google.com/p/ivyroundup/source/browse/trunk/src/modules/com.google/gwt/2.2.0/"/>
        <repository xmlns:ivyde="http://ant.apache.org/ivy/ivyde/ns/" pattern="http://ivyroundup.googlecode.com/svn/trunk/repo/modules/[organisation]/[module]/[revision]/ivy.xml" ivys="true" url="http://ivyroundup.googlecode.com/" name="ivyroundup"/>
        <description homepage="http://code.google.com/webtoolkit/">

            <p>
            Google Web Toolkit (GWT) is a development toolkit for building
            and optimizing complex browser-based applications. Its goal
            is to enable productive development of high-performance web
            applications without the developer having to be an expert in
            browser quirks, XMLHttpRequest, and JavaScript. GWT is used
            by many products at Google, including Google Wave and the
            new version of AdWords. It's open source, completely free,
            and used by thousands of developers around the world.
            </p>

            <h2>Developing with Google Web Toolkit</h2>

            <h3>Write</h3>

            <p>
            The GWT SDK provides a set of core Java APIs and Widgets. These allow
            you to write AJAX applications in Java and then compile the source to
            highly optimized JavaScript that runs across all browsers, including
            mobile browsers for Android and the iPhone.
            </p>

            <p>
            Constructing AJAX applications in this manner is more productive thanks
            to a higher level of abstraction on top of common concepts like DOM
            manipulation and XHR communication.
            </p>

            <p>
            You aren't limited to pre-canned widgets either. Anything you can do
            with the browser's DOM and JavaScript can be done in GWT, including
            interacting with hand-written JavaScript.
            </p>

            <h3>Debug</h3>

            <p>
            You can debug AJAX applications in your favorite IDE just like you would
            a desktop application, and in your favorite browser just like you would
            if you were coding JavaScript. The GWT developer plugin spans the gap
            between Java bytecode in the debugger and the browser's JavaScript.
            </p>

            <p>
            Thanks to the GWT developer plugin, there's no compiling of code
            to JavaScript to view it in the browser. You can use the same
            edit-refresh-view cycle you're used to with JavaScript, while at the
            same time inspect variables, set breakpoints, and utilize all the other
            debugger tools available to you with Java. And because GWT's development
            mode is now in the browser itself, you can use tools like Firebug and
            Inspector as you code in Java.
            </p>

            <h3>Optimize</h3>

            <p>
            Google Web Toolkit contains two powerful tools for creating optimized
            web applications. The GWT compiler performs comprehensive optimizations
            across your codebase ? in-lining methods, removing dead code, optimizing
            strings, and more. By setting split-points in the code, it can also
            segment your download into multiple JavaScript fragments, splitting up
            large applications for faster startup time.
            </p>

            <p>
            Performance bottlenecks aren't limited to JavaScript. Browser layout
            and CSS often behave in strange ways that are hard to diagnose. Speed
            Tracer is a new Chrome Extension in Google Web Toolkit that enables you
            to diagnose performance problems in the browser.
            </p>

            <h3>Run</h3>

            <p>
            When you're ready to deploy, GWT compiles your Java source code into
            optimized, stand-alone JavaScript files that automatically run on all
            major browsers, as well as mobile browsers for Android and the iPhone.
            </p>

        </description>
    </info>

    <configurations>
        <conf name="compile" description="GWT compiler"/>
        <conf name="runtime" description="Server-side runtime support for GWT RPC"/>
        <conf name="api-checker" description="API Checker support"/>
        <conf name="module-dtd" description="GWT module XML file DTD"/>
        <conf name="windows-swt" description="Windows DLL support for development mode"/>
        <conf name="default" extends="compile,runtime" description="Development and runtime JARs"/>
    </configurations>

    <publications>
        <artifact xmlns:ivyde="http://ant.apache.org/ivy/ivyde/ns/" ivyde:javadoc="javadoc" name="gwt-user" conf="compile"/>
        <artifact xmlns:ivyde="http://ant.apache.org/ivy/ivyde/ns/" ivyde:javadoc="javadoc" name="gwt-dev" conf="compile"/>
        <artifact xmlns:ivyde="http://ant.apache.org/ivy/ivyde/ns/" ivyde:javadoc="javadoc" name="gwt-soyc-vis" conf="compile"/>
        <artifact xmlns:ivyde="http://ant.apache.org/ivy/ivyde/ns/" ivyde:javadoc="javadoc" name="gwt-api-checker" conf="api-checker"/>
        <artifact xmlns:ivyde="http://ant.apache.org/ivy/ivyde/ns/" ivyde:javadoc="javadoc" name="gwt-servlet" conf="runtime"/>
        <artifact name="gwt-module" type="dtd" conf="module-dtd"/>
        <artifact name="gwt-ll" type="dll" conf="windows-swt"/>
        <artifact name="javadoc" type="javadoc" ext="zip"/>
    </publications>

</ivy-module>
