<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
    Copyright 2008 Archie L. Cobbs

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may
    not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain
    a copy of the License at

        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT
    WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the
    License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations
    under the License.
-->

<ivy-module>

    <info publication="20081216120000">
        <license name="BSD style" url="http://freemarker.org/docs/app_license.html"/>
        <description homepage="http://freemarker.org/">

            <p>
            FreeMarker is a "template engine"; a generic tool to generate
            text output (anything from HTML to autogenerated source code)
            based on templates. It's a Java package, a class library for Java
            programmers. It's not an application for end-users in itself,
            but something that programmers can embed into their products.
            </p>

            <p>
            FreeMarker is designed to be practical for the generation of HTML
            Web pages, particularly by servlet-based applications following
            the MVC (Model View Controller) pattern. The idea behind using
            the MVC pattern for dynamic Web pages is that you separate the
            designers (HTML authors) from the programmers. Everybody works
            on what they are good at. Designers can change the appearance of
            a page without programmers having to change or recompile code,
            because the application logic (Java programs) and page design
            (FreeMarker templates) are separated. Templates do not become
            polluted with complex program fragments. This separation is
            useful even for projects where the programmer and the HTML
            page author is the same person, since it helps to keep the
            application clear and easily maintainable.
            </p>

            <p>
            Although FreeMarker has some programming capabilities, it
            is not a full-blown programming language like PHP. Instead,
            Java programs prepare the data to be displayed (like issue
            SQL queries), and FreeMarker just generates textual pages
            that display the prepared data using templates.  Overview of
            FreeMarker workflow
            </p>

            <p>
            FreeMarker is not a Web application framework. It is suitable as
            a component in a Web application framework, but the FreeMarker
            engine itself knows nothing about HTTP or servlets. It simply
            generates text. As such, it is perfectly usable in non-web
            application environments as well. Note, however, that we
            provide out-of-the-box solutions for using FreeMarker as the
            view component of Model 2 frameworks (e.g. Struts), which also
            let you use JSP taglibs in the templates.
            </p>

            <p>
            FreeMarker is <a href="http://www.fsf.org/philosophy/free-sw.html">Free</a>,
            with BSD-style license. It is <a href="http://www.opensource.org/">OSI
            Certified Open Source Software</a>. OSI Certified is a certification
            mark of the Open Source Initiative. See the license
            <a href="http://freemarker.org/docs/app_license.html">here...</a>
            </p>

        </description>
    </info>

    <publications>
        <artifact/>
        <artifact name="source" type="source" ext="zip"/>
        <artifact name="javadoc" type="javadoc" ext="zip"/>
    </publications>

</ivy-module>
