<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
    Copyright 2008 Archie L. Cobbs

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may
    not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain
    a copy of the License at

        http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT
    WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the
    License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations
    under the License.
-->

<ivy-module>

    <info publication="20070821120000">
        <license name="Apache License, Version 2.0" url="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0"/>
        <description homepage="http://hc.apache.org/httpclient-3.x/">

            <p>
            The Hyper-Text Transfer Protocol (HTTP) is perhaps the
            most significant protocol used on the Internet today. Web
            services, network-enabled appliances and the growth of
            network computing continue to expand the role of the HTTP
            protocol beyond user-driven web browsers, while increasing
            the number of applications that require HTTP support.
            </p>

            <p>
            Although the java.net package provides basic functionality
            for accessing resources via HTTP, it doesn't provide the full
            flexibility or functionality needed by many applications. The
            Jakarta Commons HttpClient component seeks to fill this void
            by providing an efficient, up-to-date, and feature-rich
            package implementing the client side of the most recent
            HTTP standards and recommendations. See the
            <a href="http://hc.apache.org/httpclient-3.x/features.html">Features</a>
            page for more details on standards compliance and capabilities.
            </p>

            <p>
            Designed for extension while providing robust support
            for the base HTTP protocol, the HttpClient component
            may be of interest to anyone building HTTP-aware client
            applications such as web browsers, web service clients,
            or systems that leverage or extend the HTTP protocol for
            distributed communication.
            </p>

            <p>
            There are many projects that use HttpClient to provide the
            core HTTP functionality. Some of these are open source with
            project pages you can find on the web while others are closed
            source that you would never see or hear about. The Apache
            Source License provides maximum flexibility for source and
            binary reuse. Please see the
            <a href="http://wiki.apache.org/jakarta-httpclient/HttpClientPowered">Applications</a>
            page for projects using HttpClient.
            </p>
        </description>
    </info>

    <publications>
        <artifact/>
    </publications>

    <dependencies>
        <dependency org="org.apache.commons" name="commons-logging" rev="[1.0.4,2.0[" conf="default->default"/>
        <dependency org="org.apache.commons" name="commons-codec" rev="[1.2,2.0[" conf="default->default"/>
    </dependencies>

</ivy-module>
